<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Alex Bezek&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://alexbezek.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Alex Bezek&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alexbezek.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rails Environment VS Deploy Environment</title>
      <link>https://alexbezek.io/posts/rails-environment-vs-deploy-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexbezek.io/posts/rails-environment-vs-deploy-environment/</guid>
      <description>When the same verbiage is used in multiple contexts, it can be uber confusing for new people. On my team, I recall over the years that the majority of people getting started with us get caught up briefly on the difference between the Rails Environments concept, vs our concept of deploying to multiple environments (like dev, staging, prod, etc).
For people brand new to the industry, the idea of multiple deployment environments may be the new part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jsx vs Js</title>
      <link>https://alexbezek.io/posts/react-jsx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexbezek.io/posts/react-jsx/</guid>
      <description>For some reason, our communities as a whole often times can get heavily opinionated over certain subjects. Sometimes, this can turn into huge internet flame wars, especially it seems when there is relatively less quantifiable information to argue about, like tabs vs spaces or brackets on same line vs next. Sometimes though, it can lead to strong thoughtful debates where both sides have to do research, and you end up learning about both sides in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft SQL Server Linux Docker Errors</title>
      <link>https://alexbezek.io/posts/mssql-server-linux-docker-errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexbezek.io/posts/mssql-server-linux-docker-errors/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft SQL Server in a linux based container&amp;hellip;WHAAAAA? Thats rights. This may be old news for some, but Microsoft released a Docker image that allows you to run a MSSQL in a docker on your mac (or linux based) computer. Probably small news for most people, but for our team it was kind of awesome.
Background My team&amp;rsquo;s current project has been to create a new Rails based application on top of an existing .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linking to local images in Gatsby frontmatter</title>
      <link>https://alexbezek.io/posts/linking-to-local-images-in-gatsby-frontmatter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexbezek.io/posts/linking-to-local-images-in-gatsby-frontmatter/</guid>
      <description>Being stuck on an issue in a technology or concept you are brand new to can be paralyzing. You hardly know enough to figure out how to google the issue. Even if you do have a good search, the answer could be sitting right in front of your face, and often times you don&amp;rsquo;t even know it. If it’s not a critical blocking issue, you may try to push it off till later and progress with your work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>